betonline.com 2009-09-14

# Privacy Policy

BetOnline.com takes clients' confidentiality and privacy very seriously; personal information you supply is strictly confidential. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the personal information collected by us, safeguarding it by utilizing the best in hardware, techniques, methods and procedures. Any unauthorized use of your information, be it distribution or copying it partially or entirely, is strictly prohibited.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to enable you to understand how we collect, store, use and safeguard information relating to you and for you to understand your rights in relation to that information.

**1\. What information is collected?**

As part of the BetOnline.com Account Creation process, we will ask you to provide us with certain personal information, including a name, postal address, e-mail address and password as well as to certify that you are at least 18 years old or older in jurisdictions in which the minimum age for online wagering services is greater than 18. The name you register with must be yours.

**2\. Confidentiality**

BetOnline.com undertakes substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of the identity, preferences and other information it has collected about individual wagerers and will not knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside BetOnline.com, other than to the wagerer or as described in this Privacy Policy. 

All BetOnline.com employees are required to comply with the terms of this policy as well. This Privacy Policy provides that employees are obligated to keep wagerer information strictly confidential, and this obligation continues once an employee has left our Company.

**3\. Consent to Privacy Policy**

By opening an account with BetOnline.com, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy and encourage you to periodically review it. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page. Your continued use of the BetOnline.com services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. Our terms of service take precedence over any conflicting provision of this Privacy Policy - see our terms and conditions at http://www.betonline.com/terms-conditions.
